Juan Manuel García

Full-Stack Developer

Buenos Aires, Argentina (GMT -3) (+54) 911 6459 9095 fullsnacker@gmail.com https://ar.linkedin.com/in/fullsnacker/ https://fullsnacker.github.io/

Full-Stack developer with over 10 years of experience using the MERN stack. I consider myself a self-learner, I love to learn and test new technologies. Currently learning Next.js. I'm looking for a remote position as a full-stack developer.

EXPERIENCE

Solbit, Full-Stack Developer — *dic, 2023 - present*

- 50% of time reduction implementing CRM solutions through processes automatization.
- 30% rise of work-quality from the development and analysis team by developing a new framework based on React.js. **Tech stack**: MongoDB, Express.js, React, js. Node. js, Typescript

ArtdeCode, Full-Stack Developer — apr, 2020 - dic, 2023

- 30% of time reduction implementing server-side actions.
- 40% improvement within CRM functionalities through new modules (Invoicing, Claims, Notifications).

Tech stack: Mysql, Java, Springboot, Angular

Roemmers, Desarrollador Full-Stack — jan, 2019 - mar, 2020

- Developed an AR App to help people read medicine information without the product package. This App is currently available for both Android and iOS.
- 20% time reduction for doctors in the delivery room by developing a mobile App for pediatric medical use in Flutter that allows doctors to make a digital report of newborn's data

Tech stack: C#, Unity, Flutter.

Freelance, Desarrollador Front-End — oct 2013 - jan 2019

• Developed diverse apps, websites and solutions for clients in Argentina and worldwide (On freelance sites such as Upwork, Freelancer, Fiverr).

Tech stack: Html, Javascript.

SKILLS

Coding: Advanced: Javascript, Typescript.

FrontEnd Frameworks: <u>Advanced:</u> React.js; <u>Intermediate</u>: Next.js..

BackEnd Frameworks: <u>Intermediate</u>: Node. js, Express.js. **Styles:** <u>Advanced:</u> Tailwind CSS; <u>Intermediate</u>: Bootstrap.

Testing: Intermediate: Jest

Databases: Advanced: MongoDB; Intermediate: MySQL.

Tools: Git, Jira, Slack, Trello.

Agile: Scrum

Languages: Advanced: English; Intermediate: Japanese; Native: Spanish.

EDUCATION

ORT Argentina – Buenos Aires, Argentina. System Analyst, July 2022.

UTN – Buenos Aires, Argentina. Diploma in Video Game Development, diciembre 2016.

Unity – Buenos Aires, Argentina. Unity Certified Developer, julio 2016.

ORT Argentina - Buenos Aires, Argentina. Electronic Technician, December 2004.